ngepress.com 2010-05-29

# Privacy Policy | NgePress.com

Privacy Policy 

### NgePress Privacy Statement

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all NgePress Network websites (a.k.a. blogs) including all the websites run under the [ngepress.com](http://ngepress.com/ "ngepress.com") and [About Us](http://ngepress.com/about/ "about us") page.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://ngepress.com/contact-us/ "contact us").

Videos found on this website are not hosted by NgePress nor is NgePress affiliated with the video content in any way.  
All video content is hosted by third party media websites such as veoh.com, myspace.com or megavideo.com and other video network.

In the case of possible copyright infringement please contact the responsible parties.

NgePress operates as an index and database of anime content found publicly available on the Internet.  
Users who upload to these websites agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts.  
NgePress does not take responsibility for the content hosted on such third party websites.

Please Be informed That We **DO NOT** host any videos on this website, its broadcasted from people has been taken from 3rd party video sharing websites such as Youtube, Dailymotion, Metacafe, Veoh, Myspace, Justin TV, UStream, Freedocast and others and we have no relationship with the uploaders of videos. We just search for the video we’re looking for on Google and we embed video to our posts.

We are sensetive about copyright issues because we know that there is big effort by many people behind the work thats why we want you guys to contact us once you see that we violate your copyrights, simply send a mail to us stating the content URLs and then we will immediately delete the content and URLs.

**Email Address**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.  
**Ownership of Information**

NgePress is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Most NgePress Network websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.  
**Cookies**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. NgePress Network does not have access to this data.

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. 

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but NgePress may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If NgePress is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

NgePress websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by NgePress

**Notification of Changes**

When NgePress makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://ngepress.com/contact-us/ "contact us").
